UUIDGenerator.net - Privacy Policy
==================================

This document was last updated on October 10, 2021

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy describes and governs our information collection, use, and sharing practices. Before you submit/upload any information or file to our websites, please carefully review this policy.

### Preliminary

* We DO NOT keep or inspect any information (e.g.: text, settings) or files submitted/uploaded to our websites.
* We DO NOT ask for, or require any personal information (e.g.: names, usernames, passwords, email addresses, credit cards) at our websites.

### Data Controller

For the purpose of data protection laws applicable to you in the location from which you provide your information, we are the "data controller" of the information you provide to our websites. There may be other controllers as well (e.g.: advertisers), and we encourage you to consult their privacy policies to learn more about their privacy practices.

Our primary data controller's contact:

Nicholas Rahn  
Email: info@transparentech.com  
Phone: 1-702-441-0797

### Data Storage and Usage Purposes

Please note that this privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to any information you may provide to any third-party sites to which we may link.

* We make use of web server log files. The information inside these log files includes IP address, date/time stamp, referring/exit page, and type of browser. We use this information solely to administer our websites.
* We use third-party ad server services Google Adsense and PubMax Ads; web analytics service Google Analytics.

We and our third-party service providers (detailed above) may also store and collect data related to your use of our websites for the following purposes. Please note that by rejecting any or all of them, you may not have access to certain features or offerings of our websites.

* Use precise geolocation data. Your precise geolocation data can be used in support of one or more purposes. "Precise" means your location can be accurate to within several meters.
* Actively scan device characteristics for identification. Your device can be identified based on a scan of your device's unique combination of characteristics.
* Select basic ads. Ads can be shown to you based on the content you're viewing, the app you're using, your approximate location, or your device type.
* Create a personalised ads profile. A profile can be built about you and your interests to show you personalised ads that are relevant to you.
* Select personalised ads. Personalised ads can be shown to you based on a profile about you.
* Create a personalised content profile. A profile can be built about you and your interests to show you personalised content that is relevant to you.
* Select personalised content. Personalised content can be shown to you based on a profile about you.
* Measure ad performance. The performance and effectiveness of ads that you see or interact with can be measured.
* Measure content performance. The performance and effectiveness of content that you see or interact with can be measured.
* Apply market research to generate audience insights. Market research can be used to learn more about the audiences who visit particular sites/apps and view ads.
* Develop and improve products. Your data can be used to improve existing systems or software and to develop new products.
* Store and/or access information on a device. Cookies, device identifiers, or other information can be stored or accessed on your device for the above purposes presented to you.

### Data retention

* Our web server log files are deleted after 14 days.
* Our Google Analytics tracking code is configured to store data that is associated with cookies, user identifiers, or advertising identifiers for up to 14 months.

If you require more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

* * *

The UUIDs generated by this site are provided AS IS without warranty of any kind, not even the warranty that the generated UUIDs are actually unique. You are responsible for using the UUIDs and assume any risk inherent to using them. You are not permitted to use the UUIDs generated by this site if you do not agree to these terms. Do not use any UUIDs found on cached versions of this page.  
This website uses cookies. We use cookies to personalise content/ads and to analyse our traffic.

The UUIDs generated by this site conform to [RFC 4122](https://www.ietf.org/rfc/rfc4122.txt) whenever possible.  

Copyright © 2024 TransparenTech LLC. All Rights Reserved. [Contact Us.](mailto:info@uuidgenerator.net?subject=UUIDGenerator%20Contact)
